To be updated for web Leah Fusari PROGRAM COORDINATOR development

Leah Fusari is an experienced professional with proficiency in coordinating a variety of projects, managing training operations, and working with a wide customer base. Her knowledge includes providing technical training segments to new and existing employees, handling all aspects of operations site management, and serving as chief communication liaison. Leah serves as a front line for clients, consumers, retailers and manufacturers with in-depth knowledge of various program components. Leah has performed multiple human resources and accounting functions and her ability to multi-task in a deadline-driven environment allows her to attain and exceed objectives.

Areas of Expertise

Communication Skills
Corporate Sales
Critical Thinking
Customer Service
Data Analysis
Database Management
Decision Making
Formal Presentations
Leadership
Operations Management
Public Speaking
Team Building
Training

Education, Awards & Trainings

New Britain High School – High School Diploma

New Britain Herald Book Award for Student Journalism

First Place for Gifted & Talented Photography

Affiliation

Consumer Products New Hire Training Team

Relevant Experience

Program Coordinator, CLEAResult Remote - Massachusetts (2014-present)

Leah manages all technical aspects of residential energy efficiency program coordination including Field Representative oversight, client and customer service and ensuring high-quality deliverables. She determines Field Representative daily schedules, identifies training gaps, corrects inconsistencies with Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs) and communicates program updates. Leah ensures Field Force Management (phone GPS tracking) compliance and handles quality assurance (QA) of site visit (call) reports, point-of purchase (POP) placement photos and pricing verification data.

She drafts Program Promotion Agreements (PAs), notifications and addenda and communicates with industry partners on program enrollment and amendments. Leah also researches product specification changes and compiles data and photos for presentation in the Monthly Field Report (presented to the client).

Leah manages the Program Specific Database (Microsoft Access) and develops new databases dependent upon the program's needs. She has streamlined program databases in order to better track trainings, POP usage, product pricing and inventory data. Leah also works with the Incentive Processing Center to analyze and prepare raw data to be uploaded to the client-specific database. She is proficient in using Microsoft Excel to analyze and present data clearly and concisely.

In addition to her administrative responsibilities, Leah also serves as point person for in-house PowerPoint presentation creation and she was a member of the Consumer Products New Hire Training Team.

Property Manager/District Learning Specialist (DLS), Extra Space Storage Wethersfield, CT (2005–2014)

Leah maintained oversight of employees, handled overall office and site administration, and served as chief liaison with other departments and customers. She was responsible for training new and existing employees (district wide) on policies and SOPs. Leah led off-site district seminars regarding new sales/operational plans and promoted value-based sales tactics. She served as the primary point of contact regarding facility progress, managed local marketing efforts, and completed accounts payable/receivable and collections.

Leah Fusari

PROGRAM COORDINATOR

Prior Experience (continued)

Assistant Store Manager, CVS New Britain/West Hartford, CT (2004–2005)

Leah worked closely with the Store Manager to perform retail responsibilities (e.g., customer service, cashier tasks, inventory control). She handled human resources functions such as interviewing, hiring, training and scheduling of new employees. Leah also maintained communication with store team regarding cash reconciliation and loss prevention.

Music Manager/Café Manager/Inventory Manager/Trainer/Assistant Store Manager, Borders Books & Music Farmington/Simsbury, CT (1994-2004)

Serving in various management roles prior to the company-wide shutdown of Borders Books & Music, Leah maintained oversight of retail operations. She led team staff meetings and performed recruiting, interviewing, hiring, training and scheduling of new employees. As a company trainer, she maintained a focus on team building and representing the company in the highest ethical manner. She utilized training materials and worked closely with individuals to evaluate educational retention. Leah was also accountable for corporate sales with bulk book/music ordering, inventory control, cash reconciliation, loss prevention and shipping/receiving tasks (which included invoicing audits). She organized and performed in-store marketing events and delivered objectives in a timely manner within allocated departmental budgets.

Additional Experience (Internships and Volunteer Work):

Freelance Photographer/Journalist, HIP Music Magazine

Marketing/Promotions Specialist, Hi-Frequency Music Marketing

Street Team Volunteer, EMD Records

Advanced training in martial arts (Assistant Instructor)